as you see!
You
Zero? What a weird name, Ray. But it suits you.
Wouldn't you agree? You don't have a home, you don't have a family, and you don't go to school. You don't have any friends, either.
You see? There's no place for you anywhere in this world, is there?
Never mind.
Let's go.
I don't know.
Sure is hot, huh?
And we haven't even hit the rainy season.
What am I doing?
At a time like this, all I can do is comment on the weather.
Well, shall we begin?
I don't know.
You win the game.
You've gotten better.
Tell me, Ray, have you been eating well?
You left so suddenly.
Iyumu and Kyoko are worried about you.
That's a lie.
I not.
I'm going to cry.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
That's a lie.
Next stop, Tsukishima. Tsukishima.
Tsukishima.
fermented music
Thanks a lot.
Hey! It's Ray! He's here!
Kitty!
Welcome back, Ray!
Dinner is ready and waiting!
Hurry up! We're starving!
What took you so long?
Did you bring us ice cream?
Momo, don't be rude!
Um, yeah, I got ice cream.
And I also got you some pudding.
Ice cream!
Pudding!
Not you too, Hina!
Pudding! Pudding! Yummy! Pudding!
You bought all this?
Well, thank you, Ray.
I'll go make space in the freezer!
Springy!
That must have been expensive. Let me pay you back.
That's okay. Consider it a gift.
It was difficult to decide.
I wasn't really sure what to get.
That's why I got so much stuff.
I want some...
Oh, that's right.
How did your match go, Ray?
I sure hope it went well.
Akari said it was an important match for your club.
So...
I won.
That's great!
I'm so glad!
Feed us! Feed us! We want food!
We're hungry!
Easy! Not while I'm holding a hot pot!
Hina, the kitties are starving!
Will you feed them, please?
And set the table, okay?
Okay!
Guess what?
Ray said he won!
Really?
Great!
Nom, nom, nom, nom, nom!
Nom, nom, nom!
There!
There you go, everyone!
Wait!
Hina, you're gonna put curry on the altar as an offering?
Yeah!
Why not?
Mom and Grandma both used to love to eat curry, remember?
Yeah, but isn't curry kind of an odd choice?
Well, I guess you have a point. They did like curry.
Well, I guess it's all right.
Mama loves curry, too!
Dear Mom and Grandma, you'll find that there's pork in tonight's curry.
Well, everyone, let's dig in.
All right! Thank you!
For Eggie and Mama's pork, too!
A whole egg? You sure you can eat that much?
Yeah!
Which leads us to our next story.
Police found the badly bludgeoned body of Shizuo Unagawa in his home in Hibiya last night,
which seems to have been caused by blunt force trauma.
His eldest son, Tadashi, a university student who had been reported missing, has been arrested.
According to the authorities, Tadashi is suspected of murdering his father
by beating him with a hammer dozens of times in the head and face.
Too bad about Mr. Koda.
His entrance into the league after all this time was riding on that.
Who knew his own son would beat him that badly?
Although maybe it was satisfying to him in a way.
Well, that is, only if he were his real son.
Every move I made felt like I was punching him with my bare hands.
It's...
It's so vivid.
Like I can still feel it, even now.
Father...
What's the matter, Ray?
Are you cold?
What?
You don't look so good.
Are you sick?
Do you want me to get you something?
Maybe some milk?
Emergency!
I can't see!
Don't worry, I'm on it!
Wait!
I'll get some medicine, too!
I'm sorry.
I understand.
Just eat what you can.
Take your time, all right?
But do try and eat a little.
Huh?
Okay.
Hey!
What's with that kid?
He fell asleep already?
Talk about being rude.
Aiden passed out.
Pretty much.
I don't think he's feeling well.
When he finished dinner, he fell asleep.
How did his match go today?
Apparently he won.
But when he got here, he looked so pale.
And he barely ate a thing.
That's too bad.
I can imagine how exhausted he is.
On top of that, he probably didn't get much sleep last night, either.
All right, then.
Just leave the boy here for tonight.
I'll go back to the shop and sleep there.
I'm making a batch of jam in the morning.
Don't forget to lock up now.
Of course.
We'll help you make the jam and some pancakes, too.
Okay.
I'm counting on it.
See you in the morning.
I brought a blanket for you.
He still has his glasses on.
Good night.
Ray Kiriyama.
That's my name.
In a small town by a big river,
this is where my new life begins.
Class C1, 5th Dunn, 17 years old.
Profession, pro shogi player.
Hey, are you an owl?
No, it can't be, right?
I mean, a magnificent white owl
wouldn't just show up at somebody's house
and stand there like that on the tatami mat.
Wait.
You're a cat, aren't you?
Oh, no!
I'm gonna be late for school again!
Good morning, Ray!
Good morning!
What time is it?
Here, hurry!
Okay!
Stir it up, please!
Nowhere!
Two eggs!
Huh?
Okay.
Straight forward!
Good morning!
I woke you up like I said I would.
Well, let's go, Momo.
I'm awake, okay?
Oh, no!
Even though my sister woke me up,
I can't believe I fell back to sleep!
But first, a little more!
This is the worst!
I don't have time!
But I just gotta have one more yummy ball!
Wait!
I thought you were running late!
Oh, here!
This is for you!
It's your lunch!
I know it's kind of big,
but it shouldn't fall apart!
Oh, thank you.
And here's a fish sausage!
It'll go well with the rice ball!
Okay, thanks!
Gotta fly!
I have practice this morning!
Take your time!
See ya!
Wait!
What about the house key?
Here!
Please be sure to lock up when you leave!
Wait a minute!
If I have your key,
then how will you get it later?
That's fine!
But we will find a way in somehow!
Huh?
But that doesn't work!
I guess I'll go to school, too.
Huh?
What the hell, Kiriyama?
That's a huge rice ball!
Or is it a soccer ball?
Aye, sir.
Lucky you get rice.
I'm broke till the end of the month,
so this is all I can afford.
So, how do you guys get paid?
Is it like a monthly kind of thing?
Or do they pay you after every match?
Um, they pay monthly.
They add up all the matches we've played,
then deposit it in the bank.
Well, I have to admit,
I've been following you online.
You've been on a big winning streak lately,
so you must have a lot of matches.
Let's see.
Kiriyu tournament,
Hyokushou tournament,
rookie tournament.
One, two, three...
Oh.
Look, Kiriyama.
I don't mean to make a big deal about this,
but do you think you're making more money than I am?
That's it, dammit!
I'm not gonna have lunch with you anymore!
What?
I never really asked you to.
If you don't like it,
then hurry up and make friends here at school!
I'm an adult.
I have a lot to do.
Even though he turned pro
when he was in middle school
and could be called a genius,
he's just a 17-year-old with issues like anyone else.
I still can't help but wonder what he's thinking.
Hi, welcome!
Hello there, Rei. Welcome back.
How was your lunch? Did you like it?
Perfect timing.
Maybe we can get you to help us out.
I'll tie all the ribbons on,
then you can put six in each box and stack them up.
Okay, sure.
Thanks a lot.
Go ahead and wash your hands.
Three smooth bean paste and three chunky.
Got it.
Isn't that cute wrapping paper?
It looks expensive.
It's not printed, is it?
Actually, Hina made it by herself.
Pretty impressive.
Potato prints!
I carved the pattern into a sweet potato.
Then I printed them.
Cute, huh?
These are for Grandpa's friend, the calligraphy teacher.
He's going to be celebrating his 70th birthday,
the big 7-0.
He used to teach Hina when she was in elementary school.
So this is her special present to him.
I must say, you're indeed a fortunate man.
Having grandchildren willing to help is a blessing.
That's for sure.
You're a lucky man to have their devotions, Soma-ji.
You don't know the half of it.
The little one always gets in the way,
and she's so noisy I can't think.
Look, Grandpa!
I made it by myself!
Oh, wow!
Watchable, Momo!
It's a flower!
Sorry about that.
Grandpa's a bit of a softie when it comes to us grandkids.
Just a bit, huh?
Well, I'm off to deliver all these.
I'm going to stay for the party, too, so I might be home late.
Be sure to lock up.
Bye!
All right, let's get going.
Are you having dinner with us tonight?
Thanks a lot for offering,
but I really need to go home tonight.
I have to prepare.
I have another match, so I should go.
Oh, you've got a lot of matches.
Good luck, Ray!
Thanks.
And thanks again for my lunch.
It was so good.
Then have this.
One of our baked crescent moons.
Still warm and really fresh.
Bye.
Thanks for everything.
Come over anytime.
We'll be waiting.
Good night.
See you later!
It still hasn't come.
Could this be what you're looking for by any chance?
Ray, Kiriyama.
Determined!
Who?
There's only one of the best.
Touchdown.
We'll be right back.
See you later.
Bye.
Have a great day.
There's a great day.
Quindi.
Well, I'm very sad to say that it looks like Rei would rather have instant noodles instead of our home cooking.
Don't be so cold to a buddy! We're best friends, remember?
Oh, hey, Rei!
Help me, Mr. Hanaoka!
I found you, Rei!
March comes in like a lion. Don't miss the next episode. I'm counting on you.
I'm counting on you.